<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business on Nadia Humbert-Labeaumaz</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/categories/business/</link><description>Recent content in Business on Nadia Humbert-Labeaumaz</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Nadia Humbert-Labeaumaz • 2021</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:20:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/categories/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Build a Sustainable Free Platform?</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/04/25/build-sustainable-free-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 12:20:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/04/25/build-sustainable-free-platform/</guid><description>&lt;p>With Charlene Nadaline, Founder and CEO at Amintro, we uncovered insights into building a sustainable free platform to genuinely help people while generating enough revenues to sustain your purpose.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Kick-Start a Social Venture?</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/04/24/kick-start-social-venture/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 21:27:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/04/24/kick-start-social-venture/</guid><description>&lt;p>With Kayli Dale, Co-founder and CEO at A Friendlier Company, we discussed how to kick-start your own (social) venture!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What is a Social Entrepreneur?</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/01/14/what-is-a-social-entrepreneur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 19:03:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2021/01/14/what-is-a-social-entrepreneur/</guid><description>&lt;p>Nowadays, several definitions of social entrepreneurship coexist.
I think this ambiguity might sometimes dilute social entrepreneurs' image, reduce their credibility vis-a-vis other entrepreneurs, weaken the relevance of the insights they receive and, ultimately, harm their purpose. Therefore, having a shared understanding of what social entrepreneurship means seems essential.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Debt and SMEs in New Zealand</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2020/07/05/debt-sme-nz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2020/07/05/debt-sme-nz/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this video, I will be talking about debt funding for small to medium businesses in NZ.
Currently, we see how the media often underlines the low cost of money. While this might be true for individuals, and especially for mortgages, the reality of SMEs is completely different. My goal will be to provide insights into the implications of the existing lending conditions for SMEs and some ideas for recommendations on how to improve the situation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Assessment of XYZ’s IT Business Unit Transformation</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2020/02/13/transformation-assessment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2020/02/13/transformation-assessment/</guid><description>XYZ is a tech company whose growth was engendering significant challenges. The recurring delays and delivery issues, combined with a substantial opportunity to penetrate the German market, forced the company to undertake changes within its IT business unit – previously identified as its bottleneck.</description></item><item><title>Operational Excellence to Ensure Value Delivery During XYZ's Scale-Up</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2019/10/29/opex-during-scale-up/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2019/10/29/opex-during-scale-up/</guid><description>&lt;p>XYZ is transitioning from a small tech start-up to a larger organisation, reporting a double-digit growth over the past six years. Today, the company is experiencing difficulties to satisfy its customers’ needs. This briefing aims to provide the company with recommendations on how to keep delivering value during its ongoing scale-up phase.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Cloudy Relationship Between France and Diesel</title><link>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2019/06/27/cloudy-relationship-france-diesel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 19:03:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://nadia-humbert-labeaumaz.github.io/blog/2019/06/27/cloudy-relationship-france-diesel/</guid><description>&lt;p>After WWII, Charles de Gaulle boosted the French economy and helped road hauliers, farmers and artisans, who depended on diesel, by reducing the taxation on this fuel for the first time.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>